Ebony A. Brown

815-505-6039 • Nashville, TN 37217 • ebony_a_brown@yahoo.com • linkedin.com/in/ebony-brown-76b3a699

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Dedicated Reliable Goal Driven

Performance driven individual seeking rewarding career as a Mortgage loan origination Career Development Program Associate with Regions. Self-starter with 3+ years in financial banking processing transactions personal, business and mortgage loans. Specialized in building strong rapport and productive relationships with clients.

PROFESSIONAL HIGHLIGHTS

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Developed an internal notes template that's utilized company wide	Notary public for the State of Tennessee, strong communication skills both verbal and written, meet tight deadlines,
1 of 2 individuals nominated and chosen by company to participate in writing a training insert for monthly employee paper	Salesforce, KeepTruckin software, Microsoft word, Excel, Outlook, and Google suite products Proficient
Devoted to keeping a 4.7 out of 5 customer service score for the past 3 years	Talented in time management while working in fast paced and productive environment

EXPERIENCE

Carvana: https://www.carvana.com/

06/2016-Present

Customer Advocate Field Operations II, Nashville, TN

The customer's first face to face contact with company. Advocate sells the Carvana experience.

- Convert lobby walk-ins into successful sales, while keeping at least an 80% net referral rate.
- Amplified a training protocol that has effectively conserved company training by 2 weeks saving 20% in time.
- Spearheaded an initiative that increased office professional driving safety by 40% in a 2 week period through friendly competition.
- Creates a team oriented environment through continuous positive interactions with teammates and management.

BB&T: https://www.bbt.com/

04/2015-06/2016

Relationship Banker III, Nashville, TN

Primary point of contact, while marketing banking products to current and potential clients

- Actively prospected through cold and warm sales calls, recruited and pre-qualified new clients for financial services like mortgage loans to meet and exceed quarterly sales goals staying in top 10% market.
- Made certain all loan applications met company's standards and helped ensure regulatory compliance and best practices preparing for underwriting, while being Nmls state licensed in 2015
- Fostered a collaborative work environment by working with colleagues to cultivate better products and solutions

NB&T (First Midwest Bank): https://www.firstmidwest.com/banknbt/

01/2014-01/2015

Bank Teller, Dekalb, IL

Regions Financial Corporation: https://www.regions.com/personal-banking

04/2012-12/2012

Bank Teller, Nashville, TN

EDUCATION

Northern Illinois University, Dekalb, IL

Bachelor of Arts - Sociology emphasis in Criminology, December 2014